Christopher Yates Papers
Christopher Yates Papers
1677-1936
Yates, Christopher, 1737-1785.
2.7 linear feet
Christopher Yates was Quartermaster-General during the American Revolution. Collection includes correspondence, 1728-1848; financial records, 1732-1841; legal records, 1677-1898; military records, 1777-81; and miscellany. Correspondents include John De Lancey, Elizabeth De Lancey Yates, Joseph Yates, and Judge Robert Morris of New Jersey. Financial records of John Butler, Peter Van Benthuysen, and Christopher Yates family are included. Also includes a journal by Captain Thomas Butler, 1756.
148774
Biographical History
Christopher Yates (1737-1785), a member of the prominent Yates family of Schenectady in colonial New York, was a surveyor by trade. He served as a captain under Sir William Johnson in the French and Indian War, taking part in the attack on Fort Ticonderoga and in the capture of Fort Niagara. At the outbreak of the Revolution, Yates offered his services in the Continental Army and received a commission. He fought at the Battle of Saratoga.
Most of Christopher Yates' service was spent as quartermaster general at Saratoga and at other posts. As quartermaster, Yates served beneath Philip Schuyler, Morgan Lewis and Timothy Pickering. His duties were to obtain and transport all types of supplies for the Continental forces in his area. Yates seems to have served well in this difficult post, for he is said to have been highly respected by both his superiors and his men. Nor did he turn his position to personal profit, for he returned home to Schenectady at the end of the war nearly penniless. Christopher Yates married Jane Bradt in 1760, and they had ten children.
Members of the Yates family who are represented by only a few items in these papers include Christopher's father, Joseph Yates, a wealthy landowner in Schenectady; Jellis Yates, brother of Christopher, who served as a private and lieutenant of the line all through the Revolution; Christopher's eldest son, Joseph C., the Governor of New York State from 1823 to 1825; Andrew, another son of Christopher Yates, who graduated from Yale and became a professor at Union College; and a third son, John B., who served in the War of 1812 and became a member of Congress. Other families mentioned in the papers include the Bradts, Fondas and De Lanceys. The genealogical chart, though incomplete, should help to clarify these family relationships.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Christopher Yates Papers are organized in five sections: correspondence, financial records, legal records, military records, and miscellany. The materials date from 1677 to 1936, with the bulk falling between 1750 and 1800. Most of the papers are in English, though a few, relating to the Van Benthuysen family and dating from early provincial New York, are in Dutch.
Correspondence (boxes 1-2), which dates from 1728 to 1848, is arranged chronologically. In addition, an alphabetical index of correspondence appears at the end of this finding aid. There are also three letterbooks, which have been placed at the end of the correspondence section.
The bulk of the letters date from Christopher Yates' service as quartermaster general during the Revolutionary War. Yates' letters were frequently an informal conveyance of orders, and many letters deal with specific needs for lumber, wagons and various other supplies. His notable correspondents included Philip Schuyler, Morgan Lewis, Walter Livingston and Timothy Pickering. Christopher Yates' correspondence also contained news of the progress of the war. There is a copy of a letter from General Washington to General Gates which describes the Battle of Monmouth, and one letter of September, 1775 which gives an account of the Battle of Bunker Hill. The correspondence in Christopher Yates' letterbook (1780-1781) is similar to his individual letters and has been included in the index.
There is a small amount of correspondence in the 1800's consisting mostly of incoming letters to Elizabeth (De Lancey) Yates, wife of New York Governor Joseph C. Yates. These letters contain local and family news. Two letterbooks, dating from 1805 to 1829, belonged to John De Lancey. De Lancey had extensive correspondence with Joseph C. Yates and Judge Robert Morris of New Jersey. Most of De Lancey's letters deal with business and legal affairs.
Financial records, which date from 1732 to 1841, include papers of several members of the Yates family, John Butler, Peter Van Benthuysen and the Morris Canal Co. The folders are arranged alphabetically, and the items include bills and receipts, statements of account, bids, estimates, account books and receipt books.
Legal records comprise individually listed legal documents arranged alphabetically by the name of the chief person involved. These papers range from 1677 to 1898, with most from the 1700's. There are numerous items relating to members of Christopher Yates' family, as well as documents of the Bradt and Fonda families. The materials include deeds, bills of sale, apprenticeship papers, complaints, wills, affidavits, notes of recognizance, bonds, warrants, stock assignments, quitclaims, and certificates of appointment and election.
Documents of land transactions in Albany County, N.Y., are numerous. Items of special interest include a brief for Onondaga Nation v. Thacher (ca. 1898), known as "the Wampum Case," which contains accounts of Iroquois beliefs and customs in the use of wampum. Also, there are five records of sales or bequests of slaves, mostly in New York State.
Military records are divided into three sections: records of the British Colonial Army, the American Continental Army and the U.S. Army. The British Colonial Army material includes a few receipts, and a journal of Captain Thomas Butler, dated April and May of 1756. Sir William Johnson ordered Captain Butler to command an expedition to Oswego to guard that outpost against attack by the French. The Journal is probably unpublished, but references to the Butler expedition may be found in the Sir William Johnson Papers (Albany 1922), IX, 429. In this journal, Butler describes the course of his journey, noting all the reports of his Indian scouts, particularly with regard to the activities of the French. Butler's journal also contains detailed accounts of his expenses, consisting largely of pay given to the Indians of the Six Nations who accompanied him.
The records of the American Continental Army are divided into two groups: quartermaster papers and resolutions of Congress. The quartermaster papers (1777-1781) comprise a large body of material related to Christopher Yates' service as quartermaster general. In this position, Yates was responsible not only for transport and distribution of supplies in his area, but also for some manufacture of needed goods. At Saratoga he had charge of a sawmill producing lumber for buildings and boats. The papers, reflecting his activities in obtaining all types of supplies and labor for the Continental Army, include receipts, notes, contracts and agreements, orders, payrolls, reports, and account books. There are four copies of resolutions passed by Congress between 1779 and 1781. They concern appointments, debts, loyalists and soldiers.
The U.S. Army material, dating from the 1800's, includes several commissions of descendants of Christopher Yates, and some records of a company in the 2d Regiment of Light Dragoons.
Miscellany includes some biographical material on the Yates and Fonda families. There is a paper on the Yates family which was read in 1936 before the Schenectady County Historical Society. Another item of interest is a printed copy of Sermons to Assess, dated 1770. Other materials include a surveyor's field book, maps, music books, sermons, verse and miscellaneous printed matter.
Subject and Genre Headings
Military history; New York State; Butler, Thomas, 1748-1805.; De Lancey, John, ca. 1741-1829.; Lewis, Morgan, 1754-1844.; Quackenbush, Nicholas.; Van Benthuysen, Peter.; Yates, Christopher, 1737-1785.; Yates, Elizabeth De Lancey.; United States. -- Continental Army.; United States -- History -- Revolution, 1775-1783.; Public records.; Correspondence.; Diaries.; Quartermasters.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
A few items in the collection are restricted due to their fragile condition. These items are noted in the inventory below and are accessible with special permission only.
Acquisition Information
Purchased, 1970.
Inventory
- Correspondence
  - [General], Undated (Box 1)
    Letter to C. Yates restricted due to condition, see Restricted Material, Box 6
  - [General], 1728-1731 (Box 1)
    Letter Livingston to Van Slyck (1731) restricted due to condition, see Restricted Material, Box 6
  - [General], 1758-1768 (Box 1)
  - [General], 1773-1774 (Box 1)
  - [General], 1775 (Box 1)
  - [General], Jan-Dec 1776; 9 folders (Box 1)
  - [General], Mar-Aug 1777; 6 folders
    Letter C. Yates to Hay, Lansing and Visscher restricted due to condition, see Restricted Material, Box 6
  - [General], Jan-Dec 1778; 10 folders (Box 1)
  - [General], Jan-Dec 1779; 12 folders (Box 1)
  - [General], Feb-Dec 1780; 10 folders (Box 1)
    Letter C. Yates to Peak (1780) restricted due to condition; see Restricted Material, Box 6.
  - [General], Jan-Dec 1781; 11 folders (Box 1)
  - [General], 1782-1786; 5 folders (Box 2)
    Letters unknown to Van Benthuysen (1783) and C. Yates to Ellice (1786) restricted due to condition; see Restricted Material, Box 6.
  - [General], 1798 (Box 2)
  - [General] [MISSING Nov 2016], 1816 (Box 2)
  - [General], 1820-1822; 3 folders (Box 2)
  - [General], 1824 (Box 2)
  - [General], 1826-1828 [MISSING Nov 2016] (Box 2)
  - [General], 1832 (Box 2)
  - [General], 1834-1835; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - [General], 1845-1846; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - [General], 1848 (Box 2)
  - Letterbooks
    - John De Lancey, 1805-1813; 1814-1829; 2 bound volumes plus fragments; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Christopher Yates, 1780-1781; fragments (Box 2)
- Financial records
  - Butler, John
    - Statements of account (Box 2)
  - Morris Canal Co., Newark, N.J., 1841; construction; bids and informal proposals; final estimates; miscellaneous material; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Van Benthuysen, Peter, 1759-1779 (Box 2)
  - Yates, Abraham, 1751-1767 (Box 2)
  - Yates, Christopher, 1766-1783 (Box 2)
  - Yates, Christopher and others, 1774-1794; account book (Oversize 1)
  - Yates, Joseph, 1732-1764 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Account books, 1762-1791 (Box 2)
    - Bills and receipts, 1709-1773; 1779-1822; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Statement of account, 1734-1772 (Box 2)
      Van Slyck statement of account (1743) restricted due to condition, see Restricted Material, Box 6
- Legal records
  - Albany, N.Y. to J. Knickerbocker - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1709 (Box 6)
    Restricted due to condition.
  - Bradt, A. - Memorandum, 1751 (Box 2)
  - Bradt, A. to A. Fonda - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1752 (Box 2)
  - Bradt, A. to F. Van Den Cogard and others - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1747 (Box 6)
  - Bradt, A. to J. Vrooman - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1755 (Box 2)
  - Bradt, A. to J. L. Vrooman - Deed, Albany County N.Y., 1751 (Box 6)
  - Butler, J. to A. Wemple Deed, Tryon County, N.Y., 1773 (Box 6)
  - Clement, P. to D. Marenes Bill of sale, sawmill and iron works, 1738 (Box 3)
  - Copernol, W. to A. Laninoy Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1737 (Box 3)
  - Courtney, H. to J. Boshart Apprenticing of his Bons, 1772 (Box 3)
  - Davis, J.L. - Complaint, 1782 (Box 3)
  - De Graff, A. to D. Marenes - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1742 (Box 3)
  - Dellemont, I. with F. and D. Van Petten - Agreement concerning construction of sawmill, 1748 (Box 3)
  - Dutch Reformed Church of Schnectady to C. Van De Volgen and others - Deed, Albany County, N.Y. [?], 1757 (Box 3)
  - [?] Flyrse, A. - Will, 1758 (Box 3)
  - Fonda, A. to C. Yates Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1761 (Box 3)
  - Fonda, R. to her daughters - Bequest of slaves, 1755 (Box 3)
  - Grant, W. and M. Kennedy - Recognizance, Tryon County, N.Y., 1782 (Box 3)
  - Gray, D. and others - Affidavits, 1776 (Box 3)
  - Hearsay, D. to the Mohawk Bridge Co. - Deed, Schnectady County, N.Y., 1813 (Box 3)
  - Higgel, M. and others - Complaint, 1781
  - High, M. and others - Recognizance, Tryon County, N.Y., 1782 (Box 3)
  - Hughan, J. to C. Yates - Deed, Tryon County, N.Y., 1775 (Box 3)
  - Livingston, H. to M. Smith - Bill of sale of slave, New York, N.Y., 1792 (Box 3)
  - Lyne, J. to C.H. Toll - Deed, Tryon County, N.Y., 1783 (Box 3)
  - Marenes, D. to P. Clement - Bond, 1783 (Box 3)
  - Marenes, D. to S. Keemstraat - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1736 (Box 3)
  - Marselis, A. to J. Simmons - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1735 (Box 3)
  - Onondaga Nation v. Thacher ("the Wampum Case") - Brief for plaintiffs, tsc, ca. 1898 (Box 3)
  - Phillips, J. - Will, undated (Box 3)
  - [?] Playton, O. to W. Willis - Bill of sale of slave, Philadelphia, Pa., 1726 (Box 3)
  - Rose, I. to J. Sanders - Bond, 1777 (Box 3)
  - Schnectady Fire Insurance Co. - Petitioners for an act of incorporation, 1830 (Box 3)
  - Schuyler, P. to C. Van Benthuysen - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1707 (Box 3)
  - Service, C. to New York State - Petition for assistance, 1785 (Box 3)
  - Sevits, A. to A. Marselis - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1770 (Box 3)
  - Staats, G. to J. Yates - Bill of sale of slave, Rensselaer, N.Y., 1798 (Box 3)
  - Thomas, L. - Warrant for arrest, 1811 (Box 3)
  - Van Cornelius, F. to P. Van Benthuysen - Bill of sale of slave, New York, N.Y., 1729 (Box 3)
  - Van De Werke, J. to D. Fonda - Bond, 1755 (Box 3)
  - Van Eps, A. to J. Condry. Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1766 (Box 3)
  - Van Eps, C. to J. Van Eps - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., ca. 1763 (Box 3)
  - Van Eps, E. - Will, 1741 (Box 3)
  - Van Eps, J. with P. Luwes - Agreement concerning land transfer, Albany County, N.Y., 1754 (Box 3)
  - Vrooman, J. to J. Fonda Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1767 (Box 3)
  - Walter, J. and others - Recognizance, Tryon County, N.Y., 1782 (Box 3)
  - Wemp, J. and others to W. Marynus and others - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1719 (Box 3)
  - Wendell, J. to J. Yates - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1738 (Box 3)
  - Willson, A. to constables - Order, 1770 (Box 3)
  - Wimple, H. to J. Van Eps - Bill of sale of cattle, horses and goods, 1769 (Box 3)
  - Winne, Pieter to Joseph Yates - Release, sawmill company, Albany Co., 1749 (Box 3)
  - Yates, A. and others to C. and J. Yates - Quitclaim, 1769 (Box 3)
  - Yates, A.J. to J.A. - Stock assignment, Texas Railroad Navigation & Banking Co., 1837 (Box 3)
  - Yates, A.A. - Admission to New York State Bar, Certificate of election, New York State Assembly, 1857; 1887; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Yates, C. - Declaration of candidacy, Schnectady, N.Y., undated; Will and probate, 1782-1824; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Yates, Jane and others to C. Peck and others - Deed, Montgomery County, N.Y., 1787 (Box 3)
  - Yates, J.B., 1805-1815 (Box 3)
    Appointment as Master of the Court of Chancery of the state of New York, by Morgan Lewis, 1806
    Appointment as Notary Public, 1808
    License to practice before the Court of Chancery of the state of New York, 1815
    License to practice before the New York State Supreme Court, 1805
  - Yates, J.B. to J. Auchard - Deed, Herkimer County, N.Y., 1794 (Box 4)
  - Yates, Joseph to N. Stevens - Deed, Albany County, N.Y., 1749 (Box 4)
  - Yates, J.C., 1799-1822 (Box 4)
    Appointment as Justice of New York State Supreme Court, 1808
    Appointments as Master of the Court of Chancery of the state of New York by John Jay, 1800
    Appointments as Mayor of Schenectady by John Jay, 1799-1800
    by George Clinton, 1801-1804
    by Morgan Lewis, 1805
    Certificate of election as Governor of New York, 1822
    License to practice before the Mayor's Court of Albany, N.Y., 1791
  - Yates, J.C. and S. Southwick - Appointment as Regents of the State University of New York, 1812 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1677-1774 (Box 2)
    Two items (unidentified, in Dutch, 1696; Van Benthuysen memorandum, 1757) restricted due to condition.
- Military records
  - British Colonial Army
    - Journal of Captain Thomas Butler on a mission to Oswego for Sir William Johnson, 1756 (Box 4)
    - Receipts, 1761-1764 (Box 4)
  - American Continental Army
    - Quartermaster Papers
      - Accounts
        - Books, 1779-1780 (Box 4)
        - General instructions, 1780 (Box 4)
        - Summaries, 1778-1780 (Box 4)
      - Contracts and agreements, 1779-1780 (Box 4)
      - Orders and instructions, 1778-1779 (Box 4)
      - Payrolls, 1778-1779 (Box 4)
      - Receipts and notes, 1777-1778; 1779,; 1780,; 1781,; undated; 8 folders (Box 4)
      - Receipt books, 1776-1777; 1779; 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Reports
        - Inventories of goods, 1777-1781 (Box 5)
        - Requisition orders, 1779 (Box 5)
        - Summaries of goods and labor, 1780-1781 (Box 5)
        - Miscellaneous, 1777-1785 (Box 5)
    - Resolutions of Congress
      - On appointments and dismissals, 1779 (Box 5)
      - On debts, 1781 (Box 5)
      - On loyalists, 1780 (Box 5)
      - On soldiers, 1780 (Box 5)
  - U.S. Army
    - Commissions
      - Yates, Austin A.
        - Captain, New York State Volunteers, 1862 (Box 5)
        - Major, New York Volunteers, 1898 (Box 5)
        - Major, U.S. National Guard, 1898 (Box 5)
      - Yates, John B.
        - Captain, New York State Militia, 1809 (Box 5)
        - Lt. Colonel, New York Militia, 1810 (Box 5)
    - Light Dragoons, 2d Regiment
      - Muster rolls, 1813-1814 (Box 5)
      - Payroll, 1813 (Box 5)
- Miscellany
  - Biographical material
    - Unidentified (Dutch), 1740-1793 (Box 5)
    - Fonda, Jellis and children, 1785-1800 (Box 5)
    - Yates, Andrew, 1794; Bechelor's degree from Yale, signed by Ezra Stiles (Box 5)
    - Yates, Joseph C., 1799; Philomathean Society, Union College (Box 5)
    - On the Yates family, 1931-1936 (Box 5)
  - Field book: Hendrik Frey's survey of Sir Henry Moore's land, 1767 (Box 5)
  - Imprints (Vols. 3-5)
    - Backus, Azel, Inaugural Discourse, 1812 (Box 5)
    - (Murray, James), Sermons to Asses, 1770 (Box 5)
    - Norton, A.S., Sermon, 1821 (Box 5)
  - Maps
    - Harlem: John De Lancey's farm, 1791 (Box 5)
    - Mohawk Valley: Arent Bradt's land, undated (Box 5)
  - Music books: Hymns, carols, songs, 1864-1879 (Box 5)
  - Printed matter, miscellaneous, 1822-1882 (Box 5)
  - Verse, anonymous, undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified diary fragments, [1759?]; possibly Christopher Yates; recounts siege of Niagara (Box 5)
- Restricted material
  - Originals of items listed above as restricted (Box 6)
Selected index to correspondence
All letters are incoming to Christopher Yates, unless otherwise indicated
[unknown senders(s)] Unknown date (1 item) 1783 Jul 23 to Peter Van Benthuysen 1834 Feb 1 Lexington to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates 1846 Jan 9 to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates 1786 Feb 24 Schenectady to Maj. Phyn Ellice 1780 Sep 19 Saratoga 1780
Avery, Elisha 1776 Nov 8 Albany
Baits, David 1779 Oct 9 Fort Edward 1780 Feb 9 Schenectady
Baldwin, — 1777 Apr 16 Ticonderoga
Barth, Nicholas 1778 Mar Canajohary District to Andries Nemp
Beekman, Johannis 1728 Oct 24 Albany
Bucleth, Nathaniel 1776 Jul 24 Fort George
Chipman, John 1779 Oct 23 Fort Edward
Clark, Ebenezer 1780 Nov 13 New Perth
Collins, Tyrannus 1776 Aug 29 Skenesborough [Whitehall, N.Y.]
Cortland, Philip 1776 Aug 26
Cuyler, Ja. 1776 Aug 16 Albany
Davitt, Charles 1778 May 9
DeLancey, Elizabeth 1822 Oct 20 Annapolis to John DeLancey
DeLancey, E.C. 1845 Mar 24 Geneva to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
DeLancey, John 1816 Feb 1822 1822 to Warren DeLancey 1822 Mar 12 to Warren DeLancey 1822 Apr 6 1822 Jul New York City 1824 1826 1826 Feb 13 to George H. Teeter 1826 Jun 12 New York City to George H. Teeter 1826 to George H. Teeter c. 1826 to George H. Teeter c. 1827 to John DeLancey, Jr. c. 1827 to George H. Teeter 1828 Feb 6 to John DeLancey, Jr. 1828 Jun 27 Schenectady to Mary DeLancey 1828 Jun Schenectady to Mary DeLancey 1846 Aug 30 Schenectady to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
Duncan, John 1774 May 14 Hermitage
F., Chu-- 1845 Mar 2 Schenectady to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
Finch, Andrew 1776 Jun 30 Fort George
Fonda, John 1776 Jun 11 Caughnanaga
Gagecktoto, Cornel 1785 Jun 28 Schenectady
Glean, Oliver 1780 Nov 6 Albany 1781 Sep 7 Albany 1781 Sep 10 Albany
Glen, Henry 1777 Aug 20 Schenectady 1779 Feb 2 Schenectady 1779 Jun 28 Schenectady 1779 Jun 30 Schenectady 1780 May 26 Schenectady 1780 Nov 4 Schenectady 1781 Oct 16 Schenectady 1781 Oct 30 Schenectady
Grant, Em. 1781 May 22 Albany
Hardenbergh, Abraham 1778 Dec 20 Fort Schuyler
Harper, John 1780 Apr 6 Johnstown
Hay, [Henry] 1781 Mar 30 Albany 1781 Oct 16 Albany
Hay, Marj. 1777 Apr 13 Ticonderoga 1778 Jan 19 Albany 1778 Feb 13 Albany 1778 Feb 22 Albany
Hughes, Hugh undated Saratoga 1780 Nov 23 Albany 1780 Nov 26 Albany 1781 Mar 12 Fishkill 1781 Jun 7 Albany 1781 Jun 19 Albany
Hunn, Direk [?] 1781 Dec 21 Albany
Kettle, Margaritha 1785 Jan 25 Schenectady to Dirk VanIngen 1785 Jan 25 Schenectady to Dirk VanIngen
Laight, E.W. c. 1834 New York City to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
Lansing, A.G. 1785 Mar 12
Lansing, John 1776 Jun 24 Albany 1776 Jul 11 Cheshire's Wood 1776 Oct 20 Saratoga 1776 Oct 30 Saratoga 1776 Nov 27 Saratoga 1782 Sep 16 Albany
Lansing, Ph. 1777 Mar 16 Skenesborough 1777 Apr 1 1777 Apr 7 Skenesborough 1777 Apr 13 Skenesborough 1777 Apr 17 Skenesborough 1777 Apr 19 Skenesborough
Lewis, Morgan 1777 Jan 17 Fort George 1777 Jul 16 Fort Edward 1778 Mar 15 Albany 1778 Apr 1 Albany 1778 Apr 17 Albany 1779 Feb 4 Saratoga 1779 Mar 15 Albany 1779 Sep 16 Albany 1779 Oct 7 Albany 1779 Nov 21 Albany 1779 Nov 25 Albany 1779 Nov 26 Albany 1780 Apr 26 Albany 1780 May 22 Albany 1780 May 28 Fort Edward 1780 May 29 Fort George 1780 May 29 Fort Edward 1780 May 29 Fort George 1780 May 30 Fort George 1780 Oct 10 Albanyto Christopher Yates
Livingston, Ph. and [D.W. Dienan] 1731 Apr 29 Albany to Cornelis Van Slyck
Livingston, Walter 1776 Jul 19 Albany
Lovett[?], D. 1779 Mar 29 Stillwater
Maynard, Jared S. 1821 Aug 13 Herkimer to John DeLancey
McCall, Benajah 1786 Jun 5 to M. [worn]
Miller, Alexander 1779 Jul 29 Schenectady [Monell,] Mrs. 1820 Jul 1 Westown to Joseph C. Yates
Morton[?], John 1778 May 27 Kingsbury
Nott, Eliphalet undated to "Rev'd and Dear Sir"
O'Hara, Harry 1776 Oct 16 Skenesborough
Paige, Anna 1848 Aug 12 Albany to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
Paige, Harriet 1845 Mar 24 Albany to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
Palmer, George 1779 Oct 9 Stillwater
Palmer, Thos. 1779 May 18 Newburgh 1784 Sep 3 Newburgh
Palmer, Thomas 1845 Mar 13 Schenectady to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
Phelps[?], P. 1780 May 30 Saratoga
Pickering, Timothy 1781 Apr 17 Newburgh to Co. Hughes 1781 Jun 2 Newburgh (extract)
Quackenbush, Nicholas 1780 Dec 24 Albany 1781 Jan 9 Albany 1781 Mar 5 Albany 1781 Apr 10 Albany 1781 Apr 14 Albany 1781 May 18 Albany 1781 Jun 25 Albany 1781 Jul 4 to Capt. John Vernor 1781 Jul 15 Albany 1781 Jul 31 to Capt. John Vernor 1781 Aug 10 to Capt. John Vernor 1781 Oct 10 Albany 1781 Oct 10 Albany 1781 Oct 25 Albany 1781 Nov 2 Albany 1781 Nov 9 Albany 1782 Jan 6 Albany 1782 Jan 6 to Capt. John Vernor
Schuyler, Philip 1776 May 10 Albany 1779 Jun 11 Saratoga
Schuyler, [Har.] 1776 Jul 10 Skenesborough 1776 Jul 17 Skenesborough 1778 May Stillwater 1779 Feb 23 Fort George 1779 Apr 17 Fort George 1779 Oct 24 Stillwater
Scudder, W. 1779 Jan 1 Fort Schuyler 1779 Jan 11 Fort Schuyler
Sherwood, [Ariel] 1777 May 7 Fort Ann to Ph. Lansing